Andrei Shved

Front-end developer

I am a result oriented Frontend developer with experience creating Landing Pages, SPA, using HTML, CSS, JavaScript/Typescript, React, Redux. I have skills as an independent and teamwork. In my free time, I am fond of solving Codewars tasks and learning the technology stack for Backend, currently the PHP programming language. Ready to listen to your suggestions for project employment or full-time.



- svensk.tut.by@gmail.com
- Minsk, Belarus
- in linkedin.com/in/svensktutby
- github.com/svensktutby

- +375 (29) 763-35-15
- svensktutby.github.io/personal-portfolio/
- s svensk_a
- www.codewars.com/users/svensktutby

WORK EXPERIENCE

React Front-end developer Freelance

11/2020 - Present

Sale of PC components Self-employed

04/2016 - 11/2020

Foreman

DIST Ltd

11/2014 - 03/2016

Engineer

OJSC Belsvyazstroy

01/2004 - 10/2014

Engineer

RUE Beltelecom

01/1999 - 01/2004

EDUCATION

IT-INCUBATOR

React, Redux, Typescript

2020

The Rolling Scopes School

Front-end developer

2020

HTML Academy

HTML and CSS. Professional website layout

2019

SKILLS



RESPONSIBILITIES

Development of SPA applications, participation in the development of corporate modules for CRM

- Migration from JavaScript to Typescript
- Integration and use of Formik (+ validation)
- Custom components development
- Typescript Registration and login form creation
- Working with API
- Creating unit-tests
- Refactoring
- Bug fixing

LANGUAGES

English

Polish

Limited Working Proficiency

ororroy

Limited Working Proficiency

Russian
Native or Bilingual Proficiency